Guide to the John Henry and Anna Botsford Comstock papers, 1833-1955,
Comstock, John Henry and Anna Botsford papers,
- Correspondence
  - John Henry Comstock professional correspondence
    - G-L
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1888-05-17 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1888-08-09 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1889-03-21 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1889-04-21 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1889-04-29 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1889-06-01 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1889-06-18 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1889-07-11 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1889-07-18 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1889-07-24 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1889-08-01 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1889-12-30 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1890-01-05 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1890-01-30 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1890-04-14 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1890-09-27 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1890-10-02 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1891-01-19 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1892-03-04 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1892-03-23 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1892-04-29 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1892-05-11 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1892-06-03 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1892-06-04 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1892-07-18 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1892-07-21 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1892-08-24 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1893-10-06 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1894-02-23 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1894-05-08 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1894-05-15 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1894-05-18 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1894-05-25 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1894-07-06 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1894-07-11 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1894-07-18 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1894-10-09 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1894-10-19 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1894-10-26 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1894-11-23 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1899-01-03 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1899-01-07 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Howard, Will. R., 1890-03-17 (Box 3, Folder 20)
        student of C.H. Fernald
      - Howe, George H., 1892-06-22 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Howe, George H., 1892-06-27 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Howe, George H., 1894-04-23 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Howe, George H., 1894-10-12 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Howe, George H., 1894-10-21 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Howe, George H., 1894-11-17 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Howe, George H., Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Howe, Susan Fowler, 1892-05-13 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Howell, Jean Kirk, 1889-11-11 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Howell, Jean Kirk, 1892-10-13 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Howes, C.H., 1891-10-06 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Howes, C.H., 1893-01-07 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Howes, C.H., 1894-01 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Howland, Rufus B., 1886-08-28 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Howley, F.L., 1889-12-23 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Hoy, David Flethcer, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Hoysradt, G.W., 1887-01-18 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        Dental surgeon
      - Hoysradt, G.W., 1888-01-10 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Hoysradt, G.W., 1889-04-16 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Hoysradt, G.W., 1890-01-16 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Hoysradt, G.W., 1892-07-05 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Hoyt, Carroll Livingston, 1892-07-19 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Hudson, Louis F., 1891-10-05 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Hughes, Oliver, 1889-04-24 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Hughes, Robert Cecil, 1893-04-03 (Box 5, Folder 17)
        Vice President of Tabor College; Presbyterian Minister
      - Hull, Charles Henry, 1888-12-28 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Hulst, George D., 1889-11-07 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Hulst, George D., 1889-11-24 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Hulst, George D., 1890-01-17 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Hulst, George D., 1894-03-02 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Hulst, George D., 1894-03-06 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Hulst, George D., 1894-03-09 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Humphrey, Andrew Beaumont, 1898-11-29 (Box 6, Folder 18)
        NYC Real Estate
      - Humphrey, W.F., 1890-06-18 (Box 3, Folder 23)
        printer
      - Humphrey, W.F., 1891-11-24 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Humphrey, W.F., 1891-11-30 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Humphrey, W.F., 1891-12-03 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Hunt, E. Lawrence, 1890-11-11 (Box 4, Folder 5)
        Mathematician, Ontario Agricultural College
      - Hunt, Leigh R., 1899-08-11 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Huse, William H., 1889-10-26 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Huston, B., 1890-02-10 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Hutt, H.L., 1891-02-14 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Hyatt, Alpheus, 1885-12-24 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Hyatt, Alpheus, 1890-01-29 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Hyatt, Alpheus, 1890-02-10 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Hyatt, Alpheus, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Hyatt, Edward, 1892-03-22 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Hyde, Ida Henrietta, 1896-09-26 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Hyde, Lulu Eloise, 1891-07-06 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Hynes, F.H., 1893-02-17 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Ingersoll, Charles, 1889-12-04 (Box 3, Folder 17)
        Livery, Baggage Express
      - Irwin, A.C., 1891-08-15 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Irwin, A.C., 1891-08-27 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Ithaca, 1886-01-15 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        Town and School Taxes
      - Ithaca, 1887-01-15 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Ithaca, 1887-01-19 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Ithaca, 1887-12-19 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Ithaca, 1889-02-02 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Ithaca, 1889-07-20 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Ithaca, 1889-11-12 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Ithaca, 1890-01-01 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Ithaca, 1890-11 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Ithaca, 1890-12-08 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Ithaca, 1891-01 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Ithaca, 1891-01-27 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Ithaca, 1892-02-25 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Ithaca, 1892-06-06 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Ithaca, 1897-12-23 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Ithaca, 1900-07-18 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Ives and Ingersoll, 1886-01-12 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        Omnibus Line
      - Jack, D.H., 1889-07-23 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Jack, D.H., 1889-07-25 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Jack, D.H., 1889-08-26 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Jacks, J.G., 1887-03-30 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Jacks, J.G., 1887-06-13 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Jacks, J.G., 1887-11-18 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Jacks, J.G., 1891-03-04 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Jackson and Bush, 1886-01-01 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Jackson, Willard Cartwright, 1892-11-04 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Jackson, Willard Cartwright, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - James, Edmund Janes, 1890-12-06 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - James, Olive, 1892-12-04 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Jamieson and McKinney, 1886-06-02 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Jamieson and McKinney, 1887-04-04 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Jamieson and McKinney, 1887-12-31 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Jamieson and McKinney, 1888-05-12 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Jamieson and McKinney, 1889-12-13 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Jamieson and McKinney, 1890-09-24 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Jamieson and McKinney, 1891-04 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Jamieson and McKinney, 1892-05-12 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Jamieson and McKinney, 1892-11-02 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Jamieson and McKinney, 1893-05-08 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Jamieson and McKinney, 1893-11-06 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Jaquard, T., Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Jayne, D.D., 1891-04-25 (Box 4, Folder 10)
        Law and Real Estate
      - Jayne, E.M., 1886-04-16 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Jayne, E.M., 1886-07-20 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Jayne, E.M., Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Jeffords, J.E. and Co., 1889-11-23 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        pottery
      - Jeffords, J.E. and Co., 1889-11-29 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Jeffords, J.E. and Co., 1890-01-15 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Jeffords, J.E. and Co., 1890-02-18 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Jeffrey, Samuel, 1889-07-30 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Jenks, A.L., 1900-05-10 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Jennings, H.L., 1887-08-11 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Jennings, H.L., 1887-09-11 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Jewell, C.A., 1889-06-21 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Johnson, A., 1893-03-30 (Box 5, Folder 17)
        freight agent, Southern Pacific Co.
      - Johnson, A.J. and Co., 1892-08-22 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Johnson, A.J. and Co., 1892-08-24 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Johnson, A.J. and Co., 1892-09-07 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Johnson, A.J. and Co., 1892-09-13 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Johnson, A.J. and Co., 1892-11-11 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Johnson, A.J. and Co., 1894-06-02 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Johnson, C.C., 1891-09-13 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Johnson, Eda, 1891-02-22 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Johnson, H.L., 1890-11-08 (Box 4, Folder 5)
        Public School Inspector
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1885-10-05 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1885-10-12 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1887-01-19 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1887-03-10 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1887-05-25 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1888-03-20 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1888-05-10 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1888-07-02 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1888-10-19 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1888-10-22 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1890-01-02 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1890-01-21 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1890-06-11 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1890-10-01 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1891-05-08 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1891-10-08 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1891-12-16 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1892-02-01 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1892-10-01 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1893-04-25 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., 1894-10-01 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Johnson, J. and Co., Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-02-10 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-03-02 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-03-29 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-04-01 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-04-06 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-04-25 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-05-16 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-05-20 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-06-03 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-06-20 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-06-27 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-07-09 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-07-13 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-07-25 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-08-05 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-08-10 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-09-12 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-10-26 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1892-12-05 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1893-08-12 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1893-09-20 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1894-02-12 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1894-04-02 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Johnson, Willis Grant, 1894-04-24 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Jones, H.T., 1888-08-31 (Box 3, Folder 1)
        Lake View Nursery
        Rochester, New York
      - Jones, Herbert Jude, 1894-03-14 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1885-10-14 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        President, Stanford University
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1885-10-20 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1886-01-20 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1886-02-10 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1887-05-11 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1887-05-20 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1887-05-27 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1888-04-29 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1888-05-07 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1888-05-12 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1888-05-18 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1888-05-29 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1888-06-02 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1889-06-01 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1889-09-24 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1891 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1891-01-26 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1891-02-11 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1891-03-06 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1891-03-26 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1891-06-30 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1891-07-20 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1891-09-09 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1891-10-02 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1891-12-01 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1891-12-17 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1892-02-29 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1892-03-31 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1892-05-14 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1892-06-27 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1892-07-16 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1892-07-22 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1892-07-27 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1892-08-04 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1892-09-07 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1893-09-12 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1893-10-23 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1894-04-21 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1896-11-25 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1899-06-09 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1899-07-29 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1899-09-15 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Jordan, David Starr, 1901-01-25 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Jordan, David Starr, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Jory, H.S., 1891-04-16 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Judd, F.C., 1891-11-24 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Judd, Sylvester D., 1894-05-04 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Judd, Sylvester D., 1894-05-11 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Junior Promenade Invitiation, 1886-02-12 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Kahn, Henry and Co., 1891-07-17 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Kedzie, J.H., 1887-02-05 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Kedzie, J.H., Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Keed, E.E., Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Keeler, Charles Augustus, 1891-02-21 (Box 4, Folder 8)
        Zoology Club, Berkeley
      - Kellicott, D.S., 1886-12-17 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Kellicott, D.S., 1890-03-20 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Kellicott, D.S., 1892-01-30 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Kellogg, H.S., 1890-06-06 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Kellogg, H.S., 1892-11-22 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1889-01-31 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        National Research Council, Entomology, Stanford University
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1891-01-21 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1891-06-13 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1891-07-29 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1891-08-12 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1891-08-23 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1892-05-18 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1892-05-23 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1892-06-10 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1892-07-21 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1892-07-30 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1892-08-08 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1892-09-04 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1892-09-23 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1892-11-01 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1893-05-18 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1893-08-16 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1893-12-12 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1893-12-26 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1894-04-04 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1894-05-06 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1894-05-14 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1894-06-07 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1894-06-28 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1894-07-29 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1894-08-06 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1894-09-02 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1894-10-09 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1894-10-28 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1894-11-11 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1896-04-12 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1896-07-25 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1897-12 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1899-04-18 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1899-10-13 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, 1901-01-14 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Kelly and Co., Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Kelsey, Harlan P., 1893-11-03 (Box 6, Folder 4)
        N.C. Horticultural Exhibit
      - Kelsey, Harlan P., 1893-11-13 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Kelsey, Harlan P., 1893-11-17 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Kelsey, Olive C., 1891-05-30 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Kemp, James furman, 1892-09-06 (Box 5, Folder 12)
        Geologist, Assistant Professor, Cornell University
      - Kenyon, D.C., 1900-05-19 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Kephart, Horace Sowers, 1888-01-23 (Box 2, Folder 27)
        purchaser for CU library in Italy
      - Kerr, J.W., 1890-04-07 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Kerr, S.N., Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Kerr, Walter Craig, 1887-03-07 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Kerr, Walter Craig, 1888-05-07 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Kerr, Walter Craig, 1888-05-15 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Kerr, Walter Craig, 1889-01-17 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Kerr, Walter Craig, 1890-07-22 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Kerr, Walter Craig, 1891-04-22 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Kerr, Walter Craig, 1893-08-09 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Keyes, W.H., 1890-12-08 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Killicotts, D.S., 1891-04-29 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - King, David W., 1888-06-28 (Box 2, Folder 31)
        Photo. Engraving Co., NYC
      - King, E.S., 1888-06-28 (Box 2, Folder 31)
        scientific instruments?
      - King, Mary E., 1894-01-19 (Box 6, Folder 5)
        Anna B. Comstock's cousin
      - Kingsley, John Sterling, 1885-10-03 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        Professor of Biology
      - Kingsley, John Sterling, 1886-05-06 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Kingsley, John Sterling, 1889-05-24 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Kingsley, John Sterling, 1891-04-26 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Kingsley, John Sterling, 1892-07-08 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Kingsley, John Sterling, 1892-08-18 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Kingsley, John Sterling, 1892-09-09 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Kinnicut, Francis Parker, 1886-02-01 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        Physician
      - Kirkendall, J.S., 1886-11-16 (?) (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Kirkendall, J.S., 1888-01-01 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Klee, W.G., 1886-10-14 (Box 2, Folder 18)
        Assistant Professor Hilgard; Inspector with the California Board of Horticulture
      - Klee, W.G., 1886-11-11 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Klee, W.G., 1887-01-04 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Klee, W.G., 1887-03-23 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Klee, W.G., 1887-04-21 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Klee, W.G., 1888-07-19 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Kleeheger, George R., 1888-07-30 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Knapp, A.H., 1892-10-31 (Box 5, Folder 13)
        Principal, Afton Academy
      - Knetz, Dr. F.H., 1890-12-16 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Knickerbocker, George, 1889-12-19 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Koehler, K.F., 1889-05-09 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        Koehler's Antiquarium, Leipzig; in German
      - Koehler, K.F., 1890-12-11 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Krauss, William Christopher, 1892-08-20 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Krebs, Theodore Luther, 1890-09-27 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        musicn., amat. entom.
      - Lahaussois, Ch., 1900-04-27 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Lahaussois, Ch., 1900-10-20 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Landon, George, 1886-01-13 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Landon, George, 1886-01-19 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Lane, Sarah S., 1896-12-27 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Laney, Lydia Hunt, 1889-05-18 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        Mrs. J.C. Hallsted
      - Lang, Emma Margaret, 1891-12-07 (Box 5, Folder 2)
        Mrs. Herbert Harrison Morehouse
      - Lathrop, Ariel, 1892-08-02 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Lathrop, Ariel, 1892-09-14 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Lattimer, George, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Laurent, Emil, 1885-10-02 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1885-09-23 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1886-01-15 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1887-11-06 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1889-11-02 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1889-11-30 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1890-01-04 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1890-06-28 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1890-12-09 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1891-04-11 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1891-07-23 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1891-08-23 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1891-10-23 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1891-11-07 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1892-03-30 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1893-11-24 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1894-01-30 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1894-04-14 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1894-08-30 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1894-11-12 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1896-03-17 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1896-05-05 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Law, Benedict Willis, 1898-02-13 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Law, Docia W., 1888-10-04 (Box 3, Folder 3)
        Mrs. Benedict Willis Law
      - Law, Docia W., 1889-10-02 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Law, Docia W., 1889-10-23 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Law, Docia W., 1890-10-11 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Law, Docia W., 1891-04-11 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Law, Docia W., 1891-04-15 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Law, Docia W., 1891-06-12 (Box 4, Folder 12)